var questions = [
  {
    question: 'What is Dystychiphobia?',
    option1: 'fear of dysentary',
    option2: 'fear of dying',
    option3: 'fear of crashing',
    correct: 'fear of accidents',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Batrachophobia?',
    option1: 'fear of Bats',
    option2: 'fear of backtracking',
    option3: 'fear of baseball bats',
    correct: 'fear of amphibians',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Leukophobia?',
    option1: 'fear of leukemia',
    option2: 'fear of germs',
    option3: 'fear of white blood cells',
    correct: 'fear of the color white',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Genuphobia?',
    option1: 'fear of guinea pigs',
    option2: 'fear of elbows',
    option3: 'fear of ankles',
    correct: 'fear of knees',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Pogonophobia?',
    option1: 'fear of pogo sticks',
    option2: 'fear of ping pong',
    option3: 'fear of hair',
    correct: 'fear of beards',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Selenophobia?',
    option1: 'fear of mayannoise',
    option2: 'fear of eggs',
    option3: 'fear of Selena',
    correct: 'fear of the moon',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Dendrophobia?',
    option1: 'fear of dandruff',
    option2: 'fear of dandelions',
    option3: 'fear of dogs',
    correct: 'fear of trees',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Pathophobia',
    option1: 'fear of consistancy',
    option2: 'fear of paths',
    option3: 'fear of danger',
    correct: 'fear of disease',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Escalaphobia',
    option1: 'fear of heights',
    option2: 'fear of cars',
    option3: 'fear of Jars',
    correct: 'fear of escalators',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Emetophobia',
    option1: 'fear of pigs',
    option2: 'fear of sickness',
    option3: 'fear of dogs',
    correct: 'fear of vomiting',
  },
];

export {questions};
